RG 030, Council of Defense
Connecticut State Library
- Series 5. Food Supply Department
  - 21. Food Supply Department
    - H. Food Supply & Conservation (Box 177)
      - H06: Meetings, conferences, programs, etc. (Box 177)
        - H06: Committee of Food Supply, minutes of meetings (Box 177)
      - H07: U.S. Food Administration (Box 177)
        - H07: Herbert Hoover (Box 177)
      - H08: Secretaries notes (Box 177)
      - H09: Reports (Box 177)
        - H09: Committee of Food Supply, Reports to State Council of Defense (Box 177)
      - H10: Committee reports (Box 177)
        - H10: Transcript of mass meeting at State Capitol, 1918 March 22 (Box 177)
      - H11: Finance - Treasurer's office (Box 177)
      - H14: Office supplies (Box 177)
      - H18: Chambers of Commerce (Box 178)
      - H19: Volunteered services (Box 178)
      - H20: Publicity Department, 2 folders (Box 178)
      - H21: Printing (Box 178)
      - H23: Whirlwind campaign (Box 178)
      - H24: Posters (Box 178)
      - H24.1: Bulletin boards (Box 178)
      - H25.1: Fairs. Exhibits (Box 178)
        - H25.1: Report, Working plans for Food Conservation Exhibit, 1918 March (Box 178)
        - H25.1: Fairs (Box 179)
      - H26: Newspapers (Box 179)
      - H27.1: Motion picture division (Box 179)
      - H29: Speakers Bureau (Box 179)
      - H30: Connecticut Agricultural College (Box 179)
        - H30: Baker, H. J., Director of Extension (Box 179)
        - H30: Beach, C. L., President, 2 folders (Box 179)
        - H30: Brundage, A. J. State club leader (Box 179)
        - H30: Davis, I. G. (Box 179)
        - H30: Eaton, T. H., Secretary (Box 179)
        - H30: Garrigus, H. L. (Box 179)
        - H30: Hayes, Maud E, Home demonstration agent (Box 179)
        - H30: Hollister, S. P., Horticulture Department (Box 179)
        - H30: Kirkpatrick, W. F. (Box 179)
        - H30: Sears, Millicent, Home Economics Department (Box 179)
        - H30: Sims, J. A. (Box 180)
        - H30: Skinner, A. G. (Box 180)
        - H30: Slate, W. L., Jr., Agronomist (Box 180)
        - H30: Smith, G.C. (Box 180)
        - H30: Torrey, G. S. (Box 180)
      - H30.05: Farmer's Information (Box 180)
        - H30.05: Press Bulletin (Box 180)
      - H30.25: Instruction Letter (Box 180)
        - H30.25: Federal aid for county agents, Missouri (Box 180)
      - H35: Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 180)
        - H35: Jenkins, E. H., 2 folders (Box 180)
      - H45: Farm bureaus & county agents (Box 180)
        - H45: County agents general letters (Box 180)
        - H45: Farm bureau presidents general letters (Box 180)
        - H45F: Fairfield County Farm Bureau (Box 180)
          - H45F: Miscellaneous (Box 180)
          - H45F: Johnson, L. M. County club leader (Box 180)
          - H45F: Lovelace, D. D., Secretary (Box 180)
          - H45F: Pierpont, Seth Low, President (Box 180)
          - H45F: Schenck, Mrs. E.G. H., In charge of conservation (Box 180)
          - H45F: Wright, S. J., Agent (Box 180)
        - H45H: Hartford County Farm Bureau (Box 180)
          - H45H: Brown, E.A., Agent (Box 180)
          - H45H: Jarvis, C.M., President (Box 180)
          - H45H: Moore, O. H., Secretary (Box 180)
        - H45L: Litchfield County Farm Bureau (Box 180)
          - H45L: Bronson, Emily, Home demonstration agent (Box 180)
          - H45L: Dodge, R. E., President (Box 180)
          - H45L: Manchester, A.W., Agent (Box 180)
          - H35: The Story of Smith, Connecticut Agricultural College (Box 180)
        - H45M: Middlesex County Farm Bureau (Box 180)
          - H45M: Foote, Alice B. (Box 180)
          - H45M: Russell, Julia W. (Box 180)
          - H45M: Fay, John H., Agent (Box 180)
        - H45NH: New Haven County Farm Bureau (Box 180)
          - H45NH: Cook, A. B., Agent (Box 180)
          - H45NH: Deetz, H. D., Secretary (Box 180)
          - H45NH: Harvey, L. F., Agent (Box 180)
        - H45NL: New London County Farm Bureay (Box 180)
          - H45NL: Warner, F. C., Agent (Box 180)
        - H45T: Tolland County Farm Bureau (Box 180)
          - H45T: Gifford, J. E., Agent (Box 180)
        - H45W: Windham County Farm Bureau (Box 180)
          - H45W: Ellis, B. W., Agent (Box 180)
        - H45.05: Pamphlets, "County Agricultural Agent Work in the Northern and Western States" and "Farm Bureau News" (Box 180)
        - H45.1: Farm bureau conferences (Box 180)
      - H50: Suggestions (Box 180)
      - H60: Requests for circulars, bulletins, etc. (Box 180)
      - H90: Statistics (Box 181)
      - H100: Newspaper, "New England Farms and Connecticut Farmer" (Box 181)
      - H101: Papers and pamphlets (Box 181)
        - H101: The Relationship of New England Agriculture to Manufacturing (Box 181)
        - H101: Bulletins, Council of National Defense (Box 181)
        - H101: The New England Farms (Box 181)
        - H102: To Supervisors and Superintendents of Schools (Box 181)
      - H103: Agriculture in the schools (Box 181)
      - H104: Advisory Committee on Farmers (Box 181)
      - H104.3: Committee on Agricultural Policy (Box 181)
      - H105: Agricultural colleges (Box 181)
      - H105.05: Agricultural Colleges Experiment Stations (Box 181)
        - H105.05: Connecticut (Box 181)
        - H105.05: Cornell University (Box 181)
        - H105.05: Iowa State College (Box 181)
        - H105.05: Massachusetts Agricultural College (Box 181)
        - H105.05: Purdue University (Box 181)
      - H107: U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 182)
      - H109: Agricultural census, surveys, etc. (Box 182)
        - H109: Agricultrual census, 1918 (Box 182)
        - H109: Committee on Farm Surveys, 1918 March (Box 182)
      - H110: Farm land (Box 182)
      - H110.1: Campaign for increased planting (Box 182)
      - H110.2: Connecticut Spades (Box 182)
      - H112: Town farms (Box 182)
      - H114: Offers of land (Box 182)
      - H115: Applications for land, farms, etc. (Box 183)
      - H116: Estate owners (Box 183)
      - H118: Fertilizer (Box 183)
      - H125: Farm machinery (Box 183)
      - H130: Seeds (Box 183)
      - H131: Dept. of Seed Stocks (Box 183)
      - H132: Emergency Seed Corn Committee (Box 183)
      - H140: Labor (Box 183)
      - H140.1: Jail Labor (Box 183)
      - H142: State farm help specialist (Box 183)
      - H143: School principals (Box 183)
      - H144: Women in war work (Box 184)
        - H144: Questionnaire re women or boys as farm help (Box 184)
      - H147: Boy's camps (Box 184)
      - H151: Applications for positions (Box 184)
      - H160: Form letters and circular letters (Box 184)
      - H172: Banks (Box 184)
      - H176: Farm loans (Box 184)
      - H202: War Emergency Food Survey (Box 184)
      - H210: Livestock (Box 184)
      - H212: Slaughter of young stock (Box 184)
      - H213: Subcommittee on Livestock, Committee of Food Supply (Box 184)
      - H215: Dairy & milk survey (Box 185)
      - H215.2: Cheese, cottage cheese (Box 185)
      - H215.3: Milk (Box 185)
        - H215.3: New Britain milk campaign (Box 185)
      - H216: Sheep (Box 185)
      - H217: Dog laws (Box 185)
      - H218: Goats (Box 185)
      - H220: Pigs (Box 185)
      - H230: Poultry (Box 185)
      - H231: Subcommittee on Poultry (Box 185)
      - H231.2: Ten hen clubs (Box 185)
      - H232: Bulletins, Pennsylvania Dept. of Agriculture, Egg substitutes, shipping eggs (Box 186)
      - H260: Crops (Box 186)
        - H260: Monthly Crop Report (Box 186)
        - H260s: Newspaper clippings regarding sugar (Box 186)
      - H270: Grain (Box 186)
      - H270b: Buckwheat (Box 186)
      - H270w: Wheat & rye (Box 186)
        - H270w: General correspondence (Box 186)
        - H270w1: Lists of estate owners (Box 186)
        - H270w2: Correspondence with estate owners (Box 186)
        - H270w3: Lists of farmers (Box 186)
        - H270w4: Correspondence with farmers (Box 186)
        - H270w5: Requests for seed (Box 186)
        - H270w6: Correspondence with seedsmen (Box 186)
        - H270w7: J. P. Chamberlain (Box 186)
        - H270w8: W. P. Slate, Jr. (Box 186)
        - H270w9: Experience of farmers in raising grain (Box 186)
      - H271: Subcommittee on small grains (Box 186)
      - H275: Mills & milling (Box 187)
      - H290: Vegetables (Box 187)
        - H290b: Beans (Box 187)
        - H290p: Potatoes, 2 folders (Box 187)
      - H290.5: Committee on Vegetable Growing (Box 187)
      - H295: Gardens (Box 187)
        - H295: Meriden Home Garden Committee (Box 187)
      - H295.1: Publications regarding gardening (Box 187)
      - H295.2: Garden supervisors (Box 187)
      - : Registration forms, Manchester gardens (Box 187)
      - : Requests for garden manuals (Box 187)
      - H295.3: Manufacturers (Box 187)
        - H295.3: Manufacturers" Associations (Box 187)
      - H296: Home gardens (Box 187)
        - H296: Local committees (Box 187)
        - H296.1: Control of insects & diseases in (Box 187)
        - H296: Subcommittee on home gardens (Box 188)
        - H296.1: G. M. Codding, circular letters re insects (Box 188)
        - H296.12: Home gardeners (Box 188)
        - H296.13: Reports of local gardening conditions in towns of Connecticut (Box 188)
        - H296.2: Backyard gardens, Household gardens (Box 188)
        - H296: Bulletins to garden supervisors and leaders, and re pest control (Box 188)
        - H296: Signs advertising war gardens (Box 188)
        - H296: Photos of war gardens (Box 188)
      - H300: Fruits (Box 189)
        - H300: Handling western cantaloupes (Box 189)
        - H300p: Peaches (Box 189)
        - H300pch: Chamber of Commerce lists of retail grocers (Box 189)
      - H301: Subcommittee on fruits (Box 189)
      - H510: Distribution. Marketing (Box 189)
        - H510: Potatoes (Box 189)
        - H511: Division of Markets (Box 189)
        - H515: U.S. Bureau of Markets (Box 189)
        - H520: Committee on Cooperative Grain Buying (Box 189)
        - H540: Community Markets (Box 189)
      - H570: Transportation (Box 189)
      - H580: Special Committee on Marketing (Box 190)
      - H600: Food -Cookery (Box 190)
        - H600: Food Facts - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. (Box 190)
        - H602: Cooperative Extension Work in Agriculture and Home Economics (Box 190)
        - H620: Buying and Preparation of Foods (Box 190)
        - H620.1: Preparation of Bread (Box 190)
        - H620.11: Cereal Breakfast Foods (Box 190)
        - H620.3: Edible pot herbs and salads (Box 190)
        - H620.8: Meat - Value and economical use (Box 190)
        - H620.81: Milk (Box 190)
        - H630: Potatoes (Box 190)
        - H630.5: Food for young children (Box 190)
        - H630.6: Farmers's Bulletin - school lunches (Box 190)
      - H700: Preservation of Food (Box 190)
        - H710: Canning (Box 190)
        - H714: Committee on Canning Clubs (Box 190)
        - H724: Junior Food Army (Box 190)
        - H723: Community kitchens (Box 190)
        - H735: Preservation of vegetables (Box 190)
        - H740.2: Crop record book - Boys" and Girls" clubs (Box 190)
        - H740: Evaporation - drying (Box 190)
        - H740.2: Committee on dehydrating (Box 190)
        - H780: Storage (Box 190)
        - H780p: Potato storage` (Box 191)
        - : Frank Cheney correspondence (Box 191)
      - H800: Conservation of Food. (Box 191)
        - H800: ` (Box 191)
        - H802.2: Long Island Railroad educational campaign (Box 191)
        - H809.2: Pennsylvania Train Exhibit - Food conservation car (Box 191)
      - H850: Waste (Box 191)
        - H850: Exterimination of Rats (Box 191)
      - H900: Other States (Box 191)
        - H908: Farm Labor (Box 191)
        - H910: Request from Florida regarding organization of dept. of Food Supply (Box 191)
        - H911: Silo campaign in Indiana (Box 191)
        - H921: Massachusetts Committee on Food Production and Conservation (Box 191)
        - H929: New Hampshire Committee on Food Supply (Box 191)
        - H932: New York (State) Food Supply Commission (Box 191)
        - H927: Request for information from Nebraska (Box 191)
        - H938: Correspondence with Pennsylvania Food Supply Department (Box 191)
        - H941: South Dakota plan for increased production (Box 191)
    - A. Council of National Defense (Box 192)
    - B. Governors (Box 192)
    - C. Connecticut State Council of Defense (Box 192)
      - C904-C950: State Councils of Defense (Box 192)
    - E. Publicity (Box 192)
      - Alling, M. E., member (Box 192)
      - Chandler, G. B., chairman (Box 192)
      - Maddock, A. L. Director od press cooperation (Box 192)
      - Noone, T. F., member (Box 192)
    - G. Coordination of Societies (Box 193)
      - G18: Women's Committees of Council of National Defense, Connecticut Division (Box 193)
      - G50: Connecticut Women Suffrage Association (Box 193)
      - G80: New England Commission on Food Conservation (Box 193)
      - G81: New England Federation for Rural Progress (Box 193)
      - G921: Hampden County Improvement League (Box 193)
    - J. Industrial Survey (Box 193)
    - K. Manpower & labor (Box 193)
      - Connecticut Committee on Labor, H. K. Smith, chairman (Box 193)
    - L. Military & Naval (Box 193)
      - Connecticut Committee on Military & Naval Affairs, W. S. Cowles, chairman (Box 193)
    - N. Transportation (Box 193)
      - Connecticut Committee on Transportation, W. H. Putnam, chairman (Box 193)
    - Q. Foreign Born Population (Box 193)
    - R. Coal - Fuel (Box 193)
    - S. Education (Box 193)
    - T. Women's Committee (Box 193)
    - X. County auxiliary committees (Box 193)
    - Y. Town committees (Box 193)
    - Z. General material (Box 193)
  - 22. Correspondence, 1917-1919
    - General
      - A-M (Box 194)
      - Mc-Z (Box 195)
    - With committee members (Box 195)
    - Towns
      - Ansonia - Farmington (Box 196)
      - Glastonbury - Stratford (Box 197)
      - Suffied - Woodstock (Box 198)
  - 23. Memoranda, 1917-1918 (Box 198)
    By George M. Landers. Also includes Mr. Landers' "Poetry File".
    Roughly chronological.
  - 24. History material, 1917-1919 (Box 199)
    A collection of reports, memoranda, documents and other materials to record the history of the Committee of Food Supply and the Department. Two scrapbooks with mounted documents, one loose-leaf binder, and one file folder labeled "...supplementary note book...".
  - 25. Scrapbooks, 1916 May-1917 August (Box 200)
    Two scrapbooks with mounted newspaper clippings pertaining to food conservation and related subjects.
  - 26. Lists, 1917-1918 (Box 201)
    Lists of agricultural producers, distributors, speakers, committees, teachers, manufacturers, etc. in Connecticut.
  - 27. Potato correspondence, 1917
    Letters concerning a survey of acreage devoted to potato growing in Connecticut and the collection and sale of seed potatoes. Also a small number of letters pertaining to sale of bean seed and a ledger of seed potato sales.
    - Letters received (Box 202)
    - Letters sent (Box 203)
    - Letters regarding increase of potato acreage (Box 204)
    - Ledger of seed potato sales (Box Item 205)
  - 28. Supply order book, 1917 April-July (Box 206)
    Carbon copies of memorandum orders for office supplies.
  - 29. State Fair exhibit material, 1917-1918 (Box 206)
    Banner (approximately 3 x 6 feet) for Patriotic Food Fair, December 4-6, [1917?] and photographic negatives of exhibits at fair, August 1918.
  - 30. Papers of Derby (Conn.) office of U. S. Food Administration, 1917 (Box 206)
    Correspondence, directives, circulars, releases, etc.
  - 31. U. S. Food Administration circulars and directives, 1917-1918 (Box 207-208)
    Circulars, directives, press releases, license regulations (in binder), and a copy of "Classification used in U. S. Food Administration for Connecticut files".
  - 32. "Collected materials", 1917-1919 (Box 209-212)
- Series 6. Fuel Conservation Committee
  - 33. Reports on coal condition, 1918 (Box 213-218)
    Questionnaire reports from industrial consumers on their use and supply of coal.
    Disarranged.
  - 34. U.S. Fuel Administration forms, circulars and directives, 1918 (Box 219)
  - 35. Lists and reports, 1918 (Box 220)
    Binders containing lists of coal dealers and users, semi-monthly tabulations of dealers' reports, etc.
  - 36. "Collected materials", 1917-1919 (Box 221-225)
- Series 7. Health and Recreation Department
  - 37. "Collected materials", 1917-1919 (Box 226)
- Series 8. Historical Records Department
  - 38. Miscellaneous material, 1917-1921
    Form letters, blank forms, stationery, releases, etc. from government agencies and other institutions. These were apparently collected as part of the Department's function of documenting the participation of Connecticut in the war.
    The materials appear to be unarranged, but they are in two series numbered 3-50 and 1-50.
    - Series A
      - 3-12 (Box 227)
      - 13-50 (Box 228)
    - Series B
      - 1-3 (Box 229)
      - 4-7 (Box 230)
      - 8-12 (Box 231)
      - 13-17 (Box 232)
      - 18-24-3 (Box 233)
      - 25-32 (Box 234)
      - 33-44 (Box 235)
      - 45-50 (Box 236)
  - 39. Material pertaining to war history work in other states, 1917-1919 (Box 237)
    Correspondence, samples of forms, questionnaires, and other materials.
  - 40. Correspondence and office papers, 1918-1921 (Box 238-239)
    Letters, notes and memoranda pertaining to the collection, filing and distribution of historical material. From the desk of Olive E. Ulrich, who was in charge of the files in 1920-1921.
    One file box arranged roughly alphabetical; remainder unarranged.
  - 41. Miscellaneous material, 1918-1921 (Box 240-244)
    Material similar to that in Item 38 above. Also includes copies of magazines.
    Unarranged. Some material is in labeled folders.
  - 42. "Collected materials", 1917-1919 (Box 245-246)
    This group contains materials pertaining not only to the Historical Records Department but also to the following subjects: American Alliance for Labor and Democracy, Boys' Working Reserve, Commerce and industries, Commercial relations, Coordination of societies, Council of Defense (Wisconsin), Education, Governor, Historical Records, Industrial survey, Local committee, Manpower and Labor, Non-War Construction, Personal records, Public Service Reserve, State protection.
- Series 9. Military and Naval Committee
  - 43. "Collected materials, 1917-1918 (Box 247-249)
- Series 10. Publicity Department
  - 44. General file, 1917-1918
    Correspondence, copies of bulletins and circulars, etc.
    Arranged alphabetically by subject, with a folder of "general" and unfiled papers at the end.
    - Addresses (Box 250)
    - Americanization report (Box 250)
    - Americanization poster, Distribution; Mr. Chandler, War Bureaus (Box 250)
    - Bastille Day; Mr. Chandler - Pastor's letter (Box 250)
    - Bills (Box 250)
    - Bulletin boards (Box 250)
      - Instructions for erection of (Box 250)
      - Posting agents (Box 250)
      - Posting instructions (Box 250)
      - Posting notices, 1917 October 30-November 1 (Box 250)
      - Posters, Town chairmen not having (Box 250)
      - Specifications (Box 250)
    - Chandler, G. B., Personal (Box 250)
    - Christmas buying (Box 250)
      - Connecticut clergy (Box 250)
      - Chamber of Commerce secretaries (Box 250)
      - Maddock: Letter to theater managers re slide (Box 250)
      - Letter to store managers (Box 250)
      - Local agencies (Box 250)
      - Local agencies; Chairman, Women's Committee (Box 250)
    - Circulation Dept. re discontinuance clipping & research bureau (Box 250)
    - Commercial economy - questionnaire (Box 250)
    - Commercial relation report (Box 250)
    - Connecticut Bulletin, 2 folders (Box 250)
    - Draft copy (Box 250)
    - Fairs, War exhibit plan for State; Local suggestions, 1918 (Box 250)
    - Financial contributions, statement (Box 250)
    - Flag, Etiquette of the (Box 250)
    - Foreign Born Population, Committee on; Enemy aliens; Suggestions, etc. (Box 250)
    - Fourth of July, 1918 (Box 250)
    - French Army Band data (Box 250)
    - General (Box 251)
    - German trickery (Box 251)
    - Governor's proclamations, 1917-1918; 5 folders (Box 251)
    - Indispensable conditions of victory (Box 251)
    - Industrial plants - Clergy letter (Box 251)
    - Influenza: Mr. Chandler - Local agencies (Box 251)
    - Italian message, 1918 May 24 (Box 251)
    - Lafayette, Pershing, etc. - Special speaker's notes, Meeting of September 13 (Box 251)
    - Letter re Trip to Lebanon (Box 251)
    - Liberty choruses - J. S. Stevens (Box 251)
    - Local agencies, Mr. Chandler to (Box 251)
    - Local agencies, Mr. Maddock to (Box 251)
    - Maddock, A. L. - Letters, general (Box 251)
    - Maddock letter to Mayors re labor shortage (Box 251)
    - Map of Connecticut (Box 251)
    - Memorial for soldiers - Mr. Chandler (Box 251)
    - Mentality in wartime (Box 251)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 251)
    - Miscellaneous circulars (Box 251)
    - Newspapers re subscriptions (Box 252)
    - Non-war construction - Mr. Chandler (Box 252)
    - Notes, general (Box 252)
    - Nurses' lists (Box 252)
    - Organization and functions of Committee on Publicity (Box 252)
    - Perigord rally - clergy (Box 252)
    - Photographs, War - Mr. Dunne (Box 252)
    - Poster Distribution Dept. letters (Box 252)
    - Press Co-operation, Division of - Mr. Maddock, 1917-1918; 2 folders (Box 252)
    - Proclamations re Liberty Loan and United War Work (Box 252)
    - Prominent men in Connecticut (Box 252)
    - Publications by Connecticut State Council of Defense (Box 252)
    - Publications of the Dept. of Publicity (Box 253)
    - Registration Day, Mr. Maddock letter to pastors re (Box 253)
    - Roosevelt war rally invitation (Box 253)
    - Soldier Votes, Act Concerning (Box 253)
    - Speakers' Bulletin No. 1 (Box 253)
    - Speakers' Material (Box 253)
    - Speakers outline, Mr. Chandler's, 1917 November (Box 253)
    - Special Connecticut Bulletin, No. 1, 2, 3, 4 (Box 253)
    - Stabilizing labor (Box 253)
    - Town bulletins 1 to 15 both inclusive (Box 253)
    - Victory or servitude (Box 253)
    - Victory war rallies (Box 253)
    - War Convention, January 17-18, 1918 (Box 253)
    - War exhibit - Mr. Chandler (Box 253)
    - War exhibits at fairs (Box 253)
    - War rallies, Mr. Chandler's report on (Box 254)
    - War rallies - Chandler (Box 254)
    - War Rallies, Division (Box 254)
    - War rally (Box 254)
    - "What German Americans Owe to Themselves" (Box 254)
    - Who's who (Box 254)
    - Woman's Committee, Committee of National Defense (Box 254)
    - Woman's part in victory (Box 254)
    - Workmen's stake in the World War (Box 254)
    - General and unfiled (Box 254)
  - 45. Desk book of Aubrey L. Maddock, 1917-1918 (Box 255)
    Mr. Maddock was Secretary of the Council of Defense Committee on Publicity and of the Connecticut Chamber of Commerce, and Publicity Director of the War Savings Committee.
    Looseleaf binder containing notes, memoranda, copies of letters, etc.
  - 46. Clerical work record book, 1917 May-1918 November (Box 255)
    Diary record of secretarial and clerical work done in the Committee (Department) office. Apparently kept by Julia A. Eagan.
  - 47. Lists of "Makers of Public Sentiment", 1917
    Persons believed to be influential in the state - mostly ministers, lawyers, high state officials, successful businessmen and labor union leaders.
    - Card list
      With adddresses.
      Filed alphabetically by county, thereunder by town, and by name. Also, a card list of "commercial travelers".
      - Fairfield County: Bethel - Sherman (Box 413)
      - Fairfield County: Stamford - Wilton (Box 414)
      - Hartford County: Avon - Hartford (Box 414)